(Sheldon:)And how difficult it is to do
(Sheldon:)when she's bloated,
cranky and crampy?
(Sheldon:)Continue.
(Penny:)Sheldon, we are just people.
(Penny:)We talk about the same things
you guys talk about.
(Sheldon:)You talk about
if werewolves can swim?
(Sheldon:)See, Leonard says yes,
(Sheldon:)but I say it depends on
if the human could swim
(Sheldon:)before he was bitten.
(Sheldon:)What do you think?
(Penny:)Let's just talk
about our periods.
(Amy:)No, hold on.
(Amy:)All canines instinctively know
how to swim.
(Amy:)Why wouldn't a werewolf have
the same abilities?
(Bernadette:)Well, they're not
a hundred percent wolf.
(Bernadette:)They're a werewolf--
that's only part wolf.
(Bernadette:)It's like comparing
apples to oranges.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
(Sheldon:)Oh, and technically, it's apples
that turn into were-oranges
(Sheldon:)when the moon is full.
(Sheldon:)Hey, this is fun.
(Sheldon:)We should do it sometime
when you aren't all PMS'ing.
(Leonard:)Bye.
(Darth Vader breathes, the Joker
laughs, Godzilla roars)